<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ananke</title>
    <link>http://florentino-73.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ananke</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 20:51:34 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://florentino-73.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>First blog</title>
      <link>http://florentino-73.github.io/post/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 20:51:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://florentino-73.github.io/post/first/</guid>
      <description>Hello cruel world!
Xiao huang said he is a handsomeboy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>我的2022美赛心得</title>
      <link>http://florentino-73.github.io/post/%E6%88%91%E7%9A%842022%E7%BE%8E%E8%B5%9B%E5%BF%83%E5%BE%97/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 20:51:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://florentino-73.github.io/post/%E6%88%91%E7%9A%842022%E7%BE%8E%E8%B5%9B%E5%BF%83%E5%BE%97/</guid>
      <description>Write before beginning Before writing this paragraph, we just received the received notice on the official website, announcing that the four-day and 50 hour competition has officially come to an end. Looking back on the diaries I wrote these days, I have a lot of feelings. It is The first day to save the world, heaven and earth; The next day Newton attached himself to the body and created the formula; On the third day, he turned into Chen Jingrun and worked out a basket of draft paper; On the fourth day, he became Cao Xueqin, full of absurd words and bitter tears.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter I: The Grand Hall</title>
      <link>http://florentino-73.github.io/post/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://florentino-73.github.io/post/example/</guid>
      <description>Three hundred and forty-eight years, six months, and nineteen days ago to-day, the Parisians awoke to the sound of all the bells in the triple circuit of the city, the university, and the town ringing a full peal.
The sixth of January, 1482, is not, however, a day of which history has preserved the memory. There was nothing notable in the event which thus set the bells and the bourgeois of Paris in a ferment from early morning.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
